### Shiny Jyothi

+91 9703470788

shinyjyothi.1010@gmail.com

#### **Professional Statement**

History of being an effective team member, hardworking, eager for a career oriented position and a challenging role where I can learn, invent, utilize my Knowledge, Qualification and Skills to extend my full commitment to the organization. I as a senior process AR analyst with an overall experience of 4.5 years, excellent multitasker with positive outlook and strong communication skills. Strong customer relationship management and motivated self-starter.

# **Employment history**

1. Senior AR Representative, R1 rcm. Hyderabad, Telangana.

Jan. 2020 - Present.

- Working for US healthcare voice process provider billing for different financial classes with different denials and Insurance correspondence and urgent Docs.
- Worked for different special projects and client email account review requests. Review and analyze the account and do contact insurance if required, also document the information and strive towards resolution.
- Maintained excellent work record, consistent in performance.
- Always enthusiast in growing, took additional responsibilities within the team and also assisted members.
- 2. Claims Associate, Optum (Artech Info). Hyderabad, Telangana.

June 2019 - Dec 2019.

- Worked for the US healthcare non-voice process, we update policy benefits insurance coverage information using available resource tools and assist team members.
- 3. Associate, IKS. Hyderabad Telangana.

June 2017 - June 2019.

- Worked for US healthcare voice process provider billing for different financial Classes.
- Within 1 yr moved from Trainee Associate to Associate, worked for different project and client requests .
- Moved to another project and worked for billing rejection, cash posting, demographic information validation and eligibility verification.
- I'm always ready for all the hard work it takes or the growth of the organization and my growth.

### **Skills:**

- Excellent written and verbal communication skills
- Fast Learner, enthusiastic performer, always keen on learning and researching and implementing it at work.

## **Academic Qualification:**

- ➤ Graduated from St. Mary Centenary Degree Collegein April 2017, with GPA: 78.36.
- ➤ Completed Intermediate from Little Flower Junio College in June 2014 with GPA: 84.
- ➤ Completed SSC from Heralds' High School in 2011with GPA: 8.8.

# **Activities and Interests:**

- ➤ Participated and Won awards in Degree college competitions for singing and calligraphy
- ➤ Promoting and Organizing Events.
- Listening to music and reading books.

### Languages Known:

English, Hindi, Telugu, basics of French

# **Declaration**

I hereby declare that the above mentioned details are correct up to my knowledge and I am ready to produce the supporting documents whenever needed.

Faithfully (P Shiny Jyothi)